<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome, Dan on WELCOME, DAN</title>
    <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome, Dan on WELCOME, DAN</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Next Steps</title>
      <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/next-steps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/next-steps/</guid>
      <description>As I mentioned in CENSURF 3, I wanted to adopt a partial living style of a Baha’i. Perhaps once a week, I would try to say a short prayer at noon. The time commitment of saying short prayers isn’t just the 30 seconds of praying. It requires me to periodically check time to make sure I haven’t missed it. Every time I do that though, my train of thoughts gets interrupted so it will take me more time to concentrate again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Openness</title>
      <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/openness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/openness/</guid>
      <description>Elizabeth When Elizabeth came to our class to share her experience as a Baha’i, she mentioned that the biggest thing she grasped and eventually led her be a Baha’i is progressive revelation. It has the analogy that human history is like hiking up mountains. The big objective is to climb to the summit, but en route, there are downhills that seem to deviate us from reaching the top. After being able to use analogies to understand progressive revelation, I have a better understanding of where others come from, and how we can engage in conversations about religion, which to some is the fundamental component of human life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perspective</title>
      <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/perspective/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/perspective/</guid>
      <description>The Beach House I was invited to ride around campus to deliver face masks. I talk every now and then with this person, but we aren’t close. As we were walking towards Olin to fill up the box that Boss is holding, the friend turned to me and said, “Hey, I heard others talking the other day that your parents own million-dollar homes and that’s why are you able to study abroad?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SELF-KNOWLEDGE</title>
      <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/self-knowledge/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/self-knowledge/</guid>
      <description>Nashville Throughout the semester, I found out how my background was drastically different than everyone else. One of the roll call topics, which I still think is our best topic, is to “say something others would not know about you.” One of our classmates said that she is a contracted Disney Plus and Amazon actress. When I heard about it, my first reaction was “nice! Good for her!” While the rest of the class were more along the lines of “That is so cool!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank You</title>
      <link>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/thank-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zifangu.github.io/religion-of-the-world/thank-you/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for this inspring and unique Spring 2021 semester! You also have my full permission to show this to any future classes. Best.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
